[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 15? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "706.5",
      "options": [
        "708.0",
        "705.0",
        "709.5",
        "706.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 6? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "113.04",
      "options": [
        "113.04",
        "116.04",
        "114.54",
        "111.54"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 11? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "379.94",
      "options": [
        "382.94",
        "379.94",
        "381.44",
        "378.44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 11? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "379.94",
      "options": [
        "381.44",
        "378.44",
        "379.94",
        "382.94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 5? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "78.5",
      "options": [
        "81.5",
        "80.0",
        "77.0",
        "78.5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 3? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "28.26",
      "options": [
        "31.26",
        "26.76",
        "29.76",
        "28.26"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 12? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "452.16",
      "options": [
        "453.66",
        "455.16",
        "452.16",
        "450.66"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 6? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "113.04",
      "options": [
        "111.54",
        "114.54",
        "113.04",
        "116.04"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 17?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "907.46",
      "options": [
        "907.46",
        "905.96",
        "908.96",
        "910.46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 7?  (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "153.86",
      "options": [
        "155.36",
        "153.86",
        "152.36",
        "156.86"
      ]
    }
]